Darling, Darling?
Sailing
on the
cobalt blue!
The clouds float above the sea!
Hanging out
just me and you!
Our time is now and soon you'll see!
Smile with all your heart!
As you go past the
problems that await you!
Keep your hopes alive!
Never look down upon yourself!
Just cast a magic spell!
You will get through!
Crazy, crazy rainbow star!
Twinkle, twinkle, rainbow star!
Fast, bleeds, premonitions!
Just like the colors!
From all the rainbow beams!
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!
Come with me and we'll go far!
We're just fallen angels!
Shooting arrows into our hopeful dreams!
Dally Dally!
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!
I'm a Crazy Rainbow Star!
Crazy, crazy rainbow star!
Twinkle, twinkle, rainbow star!
Within the cobalt blue!
Seven colors will come to our surprise!
Crazy, crazy rainbow star!
Twinkle, twinkle, rainbow star!
Abandon all your worries!
Your troubles show through
the mirror of your eyes!
Let me comfort you, my love!
I'll hold your time within my glove!
We sure are fallen angels!
Just singing our hearts!
All out from up above!
Dying, dying!
Crazy, crazy rainbow star!
I'm a crazy rainbow star!
If you want to take it, I'll
give it to you for free.
Damn it.
This year's Aqua Laguna did
a real number on the city.
Everyone's giving it their best, but I
don't think we can repair this on our own.
What is that?
It's Polly from Doc Blonde!
What's he doing here in the back streets?
Quiet down!
We're here to work, Doc Clay! Now move!
Doc 3, I'm leaving this
side of the bridge to you.
Yes, sir!
Doc 5, you get started with the
houses next to Scrap Island.
Yes, sir!
I know we still gotta do our day jobs,
but I wanna see this whole town in
tip-top shape by the end of the month!
Yeah!
Let's go! Yeah!
Thanks, guys!
We love you, Galley-La!
They never let us down.
Ah, jeez!
Building stuff sure is hard work.
I admit we're a lot
better at breaking things.
I guess we're sleeping outdoors again.
There you go. Good.
You take it easy.
Just a little rest and
you'll be better in no time.
Dr.
Reindeer said Gamora's eyesight should
return if he takes it easy for a while.
Oh, really? That's great!
Go!
Come on, let us meet the pirates!
We want to apologize for
treating them so bad before!
No way!
The Straw Hats aren't
meeting with anyone today!
Our company prepared
them a thank you package.
At least let us give it to them!
I'm with one or seven nudes!
Can I please get a comment with
the heroes who saved the mayor?
No means no!
They're busy, okay?
At least let me take a picture!
All of you, go home!
Is the secretary to replace Polly Puff?
I'm highly qualified!
Stop keeping the pirates to yourselves!
awesome now that's what i call power
is this where you wanted it yeah
that's perfect thanks wish we had you
guys around all the time this kind
of stuff is a piece of cake if you
got more than bring it on you're
making everyone else look bad guys
by the way sniper king you sure you're
If our bosses are still fighting
like you said they were,
there's no point in us joining up
with them until it's all settled.
We'll stick around here and
help out while they need it,
but after that we plan
to head back to Elbath.
Long story short, you want
to come along with us?
Damn it all.
I see so in the end you
burned the blueprints.
I think it's better that way.
You've made yourself an
enemy of the government.
Yeah I guess so.
Spell it?
What are you so busy
drawing over there, bro?
Aqua Laguna was powerful this year.
I'm sure it's weighing
on everyone's minds.
It may not be long before this island
is completely swallowed by the sea.
So, what's the plan?
I'm going to make this city float.
What?
You're gonna make Water 7 a boat?
Do you really think that's even possible?
Have you forgotten already?
We grew up watching a man who
could make the impossible possible.
If you're a man, show some gusto.
He did always do everything
with a bang, didn't he?
Hello?
Oh, is that you, bro?
Hey, it's Ambi. What's up?
You're gonna love this.
It finally came in.
We're picking it up here at
the train station as we speak.
Your 200 million buried treasure.
Ah, this is gonna be sweet.
Hope everyone's decent.
Oh, hey, Kokoro.
Yo, we're coming through.
Sure, good to see you.
Get him!
I think you better wait outside.
You boys have been sleeping for days.
You must have been awfully pooped.
Not that I blame you
after all that fighting.
Well, Mr.
Pirate King is back on his feet, too.
Uh, actually not so much.
And what's that supposed to mean?
Even though he couldn't
move after the last fight,
he didn't want to miss dinner
because he was sleeping.
Huh?
So he developed the sleep
eating technique you see here.
He's still asleep?
Wow, that's so cool! Yeah!
That's what you call multi-talented.
By the way, your Log Pose should be
set after another two or three days.
What is what happened?
Even if the Log Pose is set, it's not
like we can go anywhere without a ship.
All the money we saved up to
buy a new ship is gone forever.
Our clothes, furniture, even Bellemere's
precious tangerine trees were lost.
Aqua Laguna carried it all away.
I'm so depressed.
I can't even move we left our stuff
in one of the backstreet hotels
So that's what your guests
are here about I guess.
Sorry about kicking you out, but we
thought you tried to assassinate Iceberg.
We treated your belongings as pirate loot!
So we confiscated everything.
Hi! Dr.
Chopper reporting it!
How are you?
I'm great, now that you're here!
Such a heavy bag.
Please, allow me.
If you must.
I treated the Franky family's wounds,
but I didn't let Robin out of
my sight for a single second.
Mission complete.
I already told you,
I'm not going anywhere.
You promise?
You have my word, soldier. Guys, look!
Can you believe it?
My tangerine trees are okay!
Hey, we got our money
back and our stuff, too.
Really?
Once we buy a ship, then
we'll be good to go.
Oh, right.
That's great.
Wow, baby, you guys
feeling super? Oh, what?
Oh, some folks aren't here.
Whatever.
What's with the big entrance?
Something going on?
You bet.
Better listen close, brother.
So, there's this island
that's always at war.
Wait, stop, I don't care.
If you're here to tell bedtime
stories, go bother someone else.
Shut up, this is important, listen.
For years, fire has rained on that island.
Death and destruction are the
only things that its people know.
Houses burn down, cities fall to ruin,
there's no place to run from all the chaos.
And in the midst of all this
madness, there's a single tree.
No matter what happens, it never falls.
And no matter how much
the island is destroyed,
its people gather around it
and build it all up again.
It's the strongest tree in the world.
As far as anyone knows, only a few exist.
It's known as the jewel tree.
Adam, huh?
Okay, so what?
Every so often a piece of wood from
that tree shows up on the black market
I've wanted one for a long time now,
but the going price is two
hundred million berries,
too expensive for me.
That is,
until a bunch of pirates
showed up flailing
their money around and
begging me to take it.
Bastard!
You use our money to buy some stupid
log and then you brag about it?
Told you! Shut up!
A long time ago, I decided that I was done
building ships for the rest of my life.
And yet, I couldn't help but follow
in the footsteps of my old master.
And soon enough, I found
myself designing a ship.
Now, my hope is to use that
special wood to build it.
to put all my heart into one last ship.
A ship of dreams that
can sail across any sea.
I've had the blueprints for ages.
Now I finally have the wood.
All that's left is to make it.
So, what I'm saying here?
Is it would be my honor?
if you'd take my ship and sail the world.
Wait, so does that mean...
You're gonna give us
the ship free of charge?
Uh-huh, because that way I'll know
my masterpiece is in good hands.
Trust me, that's all I could ask for.
Well, that and you kind
of paid for it already.
Gold Roger is the only man in history
who's sailed across the whole world,
and his ship, the Otto Jackson,
was made from a jewel tree as well.
Mark my words I'll show you the
best damn ship you've ever seen yeah
you're a ship right after all you can
pretend all you like but in the end
you're just like old Tom ain't ya
guess you're right
I get it now it took
a while but I I think I finally understand
the pride Tom felt when he died.
Yeah!
You're the best, Franky! Thank you!
We'd be happy to take your show!
All right!
Now on to the next island! Luffy!
We have a new show! Get him! Get him!
This is bad!
I didn't think those bastards
would come after us so soon.
Damn it, I bet Luffy's
still sleeping, too.
I got to warn him before it's too late.
No way.
It's the Navy.
They're here to arrest the pirates.
Even after they saved the mayor's
life, they won't show them any mercy.
Hey, you see that over there?
That's Vice Admiral Garp's ship,
straight from headquarters.
Wait, did you say Garp?
The same Garp that nearly
captured Gold Roger?
Over and over again, he's a living legend.
They're not messing around.
If they send him, if they don't
run, those pirates are finished.
What the hell's going on here?
Don't tell me this is the same beach.
I don't have time for this crap right now.
Now, hold on, sir.
The only person here is our president, Mr.
Iceberg.
Toobin, I know you're
hiding those pirates.
I swear, we're not.
Hey, you can't go inside.
Hold on.
The Straw Hats are heroes.
Hey, shut up.
All right, you two. Wait here.
Yes, sir!
What the hell?
What's going on?
Pardon me, but are you
folks the Straw Hat Pirates?
You see, I have some friends here that
would like to share our word with Monkey D.
Luffy.
The Navy!
Rise and shine!
Ow!
That hurt!
What happened?
Why would one little
punch hurt you so much?
You're made of rubber!
It's because there is no
defense against a fist of love.
You've been getting in a lot
of trouble lately, haven't you?
Luffy.
Grandpa?
It's been a while.
I think you owe me an apology, boy!
You've been up to no good.
But isn't that the name of the Navy
hero that fought against Gold Roger?
Luffy, is this Navy guy
really your grandpa? Sure is!
No matter what, don't try to fight him!
He'll kill you just like he almost killed
me over and over when I was little.
Now, now, you're gonna
give them the wrong idea,
although I admit I did throw
you into a ravine that one time,
and I left you in the
jungle a few times too,
and sure there were those times I
sent you sailing on those balloons,
but I didn't do it to kill you,
I did it to make you a man.
I
see.
So this is where all of
Luffy's endurance comes from.
This is why everything
rolls off of him when
I left you and Ace with
my friend for training.
I thought everything would work out fine,
but I turned my back
and you end up like this.
I wanted to make you into a navy man.
You stinking ingrate.
How the heck did you become a criminal?
I told you a million times.
I wanted to be a pirate.
It's not my fault you wouldn't listen.
This is all that damn redhead's fault.
The fool. I.
I wouldn't even be alive
if it wasn't for Sexy.
Shut up.
Shut up. Huh?
Is that any way to speak to your grandpa?
Oh right.
I'm sorry.
We're all set for!
A captain's been captured by the Marines!
Luffy!
Help! No! This is bad.
If we try to help Luffy,
then all those Marines outside are
going to rush in and attack us!
They're asleep?!
So wait, what are we supposed to do here?
I've never been in a
situation like this before.
Oh no, did I fall asleep again?
Wake up and take your lecture like a man!
Don't you dare goes off on
me when I'm yelling at you?
That's his grandfather.
Well, it's no wonder Luffy
never talked about his family.
This is crazy
Speaking of that red-headed
pirate friend of yours,
do you have any clue what kind of
dangerous business he's involved in?
No, I haven't heard anything
about Shanks in a long time.
Is he okay? What's he up to?
Is he okay? Of course.
There's as many pirates out there
as there are stars in the sky.
But that redhead's one of the brightest.
He's in the same class
as Whitebeard, even.
There are only four pirates
as powerful as that,
and they rule over the second half
of the Grand Line, like kings!
They're the four emperors!
The seven warlords and us folks of
the navy have allied against them.
The idea is to create a balance of power.
If any one of these three forces
grew stronger than the others,
then the peace we worked so hard to
protect would come crumbling down.
I don't really get it,
but I'm glad he's okay.
Man, brings back memories, huh?
Luffy has connections
to red-haired Shanks?
That's where he got his Straw Hat from.
Shanks asked him to take care of it.
I had no idea he was such
an important guy, though.
It's over here, Zoro!
Damn it, we're too late!
Anyway, good luck with the Navy.
I'm sorry again.
We shouldn't have tried to mug you.
That was a mistake.
Don't worry about it.
Thanks for showing me the way here.
See ya.
What's going on out there?
It's the pirate hunter.
He seems to be going on
some sort of rampage.
He's from Luffy's crew, huh?
He looks pretty tough.
Go ahead, you two.
Give him hell, sir
Cookery knives, huh?
Interesting choice of a weapon.
You've got there
For you, Jack?
Are you okay?
What happened, boys?
You're no match at all.
You're as tough as I thought you'd be.
That was a nice one, anyway.
I give...
Hi, Luffy. Hi, Zoro.
It's been a while.
Do you know who I am?
Uh, no.
Look, it's me. It's Kobe.
You mean you don't remember me?
Kobe, huh?
I do have a friend named Kobe.
But the Kobe I know is a
whole lot smaller than you.
Sorry.
Nope, that's the right Kobe.
The crybaby, good-for-nothing
Kobe from before.
No way!
Yeah, that's him.
But why is he on the Grand Line?
To be honest, I'm not a
commissioned Navy officer yet.
But when I heard you
guys were in the area,
I had to stop by and say hello
while I still had the chance.
If it wasn't for you two, we
wouldn't be where we are today.
Hmph.
Well, I wouldn't go quite that far.
A lot of stuff happened,
but long story short,
we ended up being trained by
Vice Admiral Garp himself.
Must have been hard work!
Man, you grew so much from before,
I didn't even recognize you!
It's crazy!
The Kobe I remember was
a pudgy little dorky guy!
I'm sure you're worn out
after all that happened.
Sorry to bother you.
Nah, it's fine!
I haven't seen you in ages!
We gotta celebrate!
Hey, you bastards!
Hold on a second!
You didn't recognize me at all, huh?
Who the hell are you?
It's me! See? Me!
No, I don't see. Just tell me.
Get a clue, guys.
It's Helmepo, Captain
Morgan's son, Helmepo.
Surely you remember now.
I had you tied up you were almost
executed because of me Zoro.
You couldn't possibly
forget that could you
Really guys?
Stop giving me such a hard time!
No one likes a bully.
Zoro you seem to be handling
this well, don't you agree?
No, stop!
I worked so hard!
I made empty threats?
I was always talking about my daddy?
Oh, that guy.
What do you mean, that guy?
Yeah, right.
You sucked.
No wonder I forgot.
I wanted to forgive
them, but I just can't.
I'm so sorry, Koby.
You just have to accept the
past and move on, Helmepo.
He still sucks.
Looks like it.
Now, I've got a job for
you boys. Sir! This wall?
Fix it. What? Are you kidding?
If you were going to have us fix it,
why'd you break it in the first place?
Because walking through a door
doesn't make much of an impression.
The only impression you're
making here is a bad one.
Okay, we'll fix the wall, but it's
your fault, so you've got to help us.
What?
All right.
So this grandpa of yours
is really famous. Beats me.
I never really asked him about his job.
By the way, Luffy, I heard you met
your old man a while back. Huh? My dad?
No, I don't think so.
I didn't even think I had a dad.
That's a shame.
I thought he'd introduce himself to you.
From what I hear, he saw
you off back at Loguetown.
I remember what happened, but I
sure don't remember Luffy's father.
Uh, could you give me a hint here?
What's dad like?
The name of your father is Monkey D.
Dragon, the revolutionary.
Dragon, huh?
That dragon?
The revolutionary has a son?
Even though he's famous,
Luffy didn't know.
Wait, Dragon is Vice Admiral Garp's son?
What kind of crazy messed
up family have they got?
Come to think of it, I never
heard Dragon's full name before.
What's the deal, you guys?
Why is everyone freaking out so much?
Are you kidding?
You're trying to tell me you've
never heard of Dragon before?
He's a dangerous man.
Like, really dangerous.
Um, Robin?
I'm not exactly sure how
I should explain this one.
Pirates like us are
enemies with the navy but.
We don't usually attack them on
our own but there is one group
that is directly opposing the
authority of the world government.
The revolutionary army and the man
at the head of that group is Dragon.
By now his ideology has spread to many
nations causing worldwide rebellion.
The government's hold has already
collapsed in a number of regions.
Naturally, the government is furious.
They've labeled Dragon as
the world's worst criminal
and will stop at absolutely
nothing to hunt him down.
The problem is that no one
knows a single thing about him.
He's very mysterious.
And yet...
And yet what?
Uh, that was a mistake, huh?
I probably shouldn't
have said all that stuff.
I take it all back.
Forget it, okay?
What?